<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><ServiceComplementaire xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" ID="R34182" type="Formulaire" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../Schemas/3.4/ServiceComplementaire.xsd" spUrl="https://www.service-public.fr/professionnels-entreprises/vosdroits/R34182"><dc:title>Declaration of registration of a business with employees but no fixed establishment in France (English version) (Formulaire)</dc:title><dc:creator>Direction de l'information légale et administrative</dc:creator><dc:description>Enables foreign companies to complete several formalities related to the registration of the company in France. Upon receipt of this form, the Urssaf collection office of the Bas-Rhin region will carry out all administrative formalities with: - Insee (the French office for statistics) - France Travail (anciennement Pôle emploi) (unemployment insurance agency) - the direction régionale des entreprises, de la concurrence, de la consommation, du travail et de l'emploi, Dirrecte (regional office for business, competition, consumption, work and employment) - Caisse d'assurance retraite et de la santé au travail (sickness fund) Once the company's registration is complete, a Siret identification number will be assigned to the company.</dc:description><dc:publisher>Direction de l'information légale et administrative</dc:publisher><dc:contributor>Direction de l'information légale et administrative (Premier ministre)</dc:contributor><dc:date>modified 2018-06-11</dc:date><dc:type>Formulaire</dc:type><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><dc:identifier>R34182</dc:identifier><dc:language>Fr</dc:language><dc:coverage>France entière</dc:coverage><dc:rights>https://www.service-public.fr/a-propos/mentions-legales</dc:rights><SurTitre>Formulaire</SurTitre><Audience>Professionnels</Audience><Canal>www.service-public.fr</Canal><FilDAriane><Niveau ID="Professionnels">Accueil professionnels</Niveau><Niveau ID="servicesEnLigne" type="Liste - Service en ligne">Services en ligne et formulaires</Niveau><Niveau ID="R34182" type="Formulaire">Declaration of registration of a business with employees but no fixed establishment in France (English version)</Niveau></FilDAriane><AutreNumero>EO form</AutreNumero><Texte><Paragraphe>Enables foreign companies to complete several formalities related to the registration of the company in France. Upon receipt of this form, the Urssaf collection office of the Bas-Rhin region will carry out all administrative formalities with:</Paragraphe><Liste type="puce"><Item><Paragraphe>Insee (the French office for statistics)</Paragraphe></Item><Item><Paragraphe>France Travail (anciennement Pôle emploi) (unemployment insurance agency)</Paragraphe></Item><Item><Paragraphe>the direction régionale des entreprises, de la concurrence, de la consommation, du travail et de l'emploi, Dirrecte (regional office for business, competition, consumption, work and employment)</Paragraphe></Item><Item><Paragraphe>Caisse d'assurance retraite et de la santé au travail (sickness fund)</Paragraphe></Item></Liste><Paragraphe>Once the company's registration is complete, a Siret identification number will be assigned to the company.</Paragraphe></Texte><LienWeb URL="http://www.net-entreprises.fr/vos-declarations-en-ligne/entreprises-etrangeres/#english-version"><Source>Urssaf</Source></LienWeb><NoticeLiee ID="R34184" URL="http://www.net-entreprises.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/guide_form_E0.pdf" type="Notice" format="application/pdf" poids="0">Guide of instructions for completing Form E0</NoticeLiee><OuSAdresser ID="R31518" sve="non" type="Centre de contact"><Titre>Centre national des firmes étrangères (CNFE)</Titre><Source ID="R30863">Urssaf</Source><Texte><Paragraphe>Permet aux entreprises étrangères sans établissement en France d'employer un ou plusieurs salariés sur le territoire français, de les affilier au régime français de Sécurité sociale et de payer les cotisations et contributions pour financer leur protection sociale.</Paragraphe><Chapitre><Titre><Paragraphe>Par courrier</Paragraphe></Titre><Paragraphe>Urssaf Alsace</Paragraphe><Paragraphe>16, rue Contades</Paragraphe><Paragraphe>67945 Strasbourg Cedex 9</Paragraphe><Paragraphe>France</Paragraphe></Chapitre><Chapitre><Titre><Paragraphe>Par téléphone</Paragraphe></Titre><Paragraphe><MiseEnEvidence>39 57</MiseEnEvidence></Paragraphe><Paragraphe>Numéro violet ou majoré : coût d'un appel vers un numéro fixe + service payant, depuis un téléphone fixe ou mobile</Paragraphe><Paragraphe>Pour connaître le tarif, écoutez le message en début d'appel</Paragraphe></Chapitre><Chapitre><Titre><Paragraphe>Par fax</Paragraphe></Titre><Paragraphe>+33 3 69 32 30 08</Paragraphe></Chapitre><Chapitre><Titre><Paragraphe>Par courriel</Paragraphe></Titre><Paragraphe>cnfe.strasbourg@urssaf.fr</Paragraphe></Chapitre></Texte></OuSAdresser><OuSAdresserSupport ID="R47050" type="Support" audience="Professionnels"><Titre>Contact support Net-Entreprises</Titre><Texte><Paragraphe>Accès à la page d'<LienExterne URL="http://www.net-entreprises.fr/aide/#nous-contacter">aide et de contact</LienExterne></Paragraphe></Texte></OuSAdresserSupport></ServiceComplementaire>